MRS. WOLOWITZ:
Howard, have you seen
(Mrs Wolowitz(off):)my girdle?!
(Howard:)No, Ma!
(Mrs Wolowitz:)I can't find it, and I'm late
for my Weight Watchers meeting!
(Howard:)Maybe it committed suicide!
(Howard:)Leave me alone!
(Howard:)Now, where were we?
(Bernadette:)I believe you
were about
(Bernadette:)to rip off my uniform
with your teeth.
Bernadette?!
(Howard:)What are you doing here?
(Katee Sackhoff:)Well, if I had to
guess, I'd say I'm here
(Katee Sackhoff:)because you saw me
earlier this evening,
(Katee Sackhoff:)and you're still
hung up on me.
(Howard:)No, I'm not.
(Bernadette:)Clearly you are.
(Bernadette:)Otherwise, based
on past experience,
(Bernadette:)we'd be done by now.
(Howard:)Okay,
I'm a little confused here.
GEORGE TAKEI:
Oh, my.
(George Takei:)Can I help?
(Howard:)Not that kind of confused.
(Bernadette:)What's George
Takei doing here?
(Katee Sackhoff:)Howard, do you have
latent homosexual tendencies?
(Howard:)No, of course not.
(George Takei:)So you say.
(George Takei:)Yet, here I am.